Hopefully, you are now feeling more confident and
我希望你现在更有信心
have a deeper conceptual understanding of RNNS.
更加深入地了解循环神经网络
But how do we train such networks?
不过我们如何训练这些网络呢？
How can we find a good set of weights that would minimize the error?
我们怎样找到一组好的权重 可以最小化误差呢？
You will see that our training framework will be similar to what we've seen before,
你会发现我们的训练框架与之前见到的类似
with a slight change in the back propagation algorithm.
但其中的反向传播算法中具有轻微改变
When training RNNS, we use what we call back propagation through time.
训练循环神经网络时 我们使用基于时间的反向传播算法
For simplicity reasons, let's decide that from this point,
为了简便 我们决定 从此刻起
whenever I refer to partial derivatives,
不管什么时候提到偏导数
I will simply say derivatives,
我都会简称为导数
as I will need to refer to those quite often.
因为我会不断涉及到这些
And before I start,
在我开始前
just a small reminder.
有个小小的提醒
If you feel that taking notes has been working for you,
如果你觉得记笔记很有效
please continue to do so.
那就继续使用这个方法
To better understand back propagation through time,
为了更好地理解基于时间的反向传播算法
we need a few notational definitions.
我们需要一些符号定义
We've seen them before in a previous video but let's emphasize them again.
在之前的视频中我们见到过它们 但是需要再次强调一下
The state vector S_of_t is given by applying
通过应用激活函数 如双曲正切
an activation function let's say a hyperbolic tangent for example,
对状态向量 St 进行赋值
to the sum of the product of the input vector X_of_t with a weight matrix Wx,
得到输入向量 Xt 乘以权重矩阵 Wx 的乘积
and the product of the previous state vector S_of_t minus 1 with the weight matrix Ws.
加上之前的状态向量 St-1 乘以权重矩阵 Ws 的乘积
The output at time t simply equals to the product of the state vector S_of_t,
时间 t 的输出等于状态向量 St
with a weight matrix Wy,
和权重矩阵 Wy 的乘积
unless you're also using a soft max function for example.
除非你也使用 Softmax 函数
And the loss function,
而损失函数
the square error E_of_t equals to the square of the difference between the
即平方差 Et 等于时间 t 的理想输出和
desired and the network output at time t. In previous lessons,
网络输出的方差 在之前的课程里
you've seen other error functions such as the cross entropy loss for example.
你见过其他误差函数 如交叉熵损失函数
But for consistency, we will stay with the same error we've seen so far in this lesson.
不过为了保持一致 我们使用这节课程中相同误差
In back propagation through time,
在基于时间的反向传播中
we don't independently train the system at a specific time t. What we do,
我们不会单独在特定时间 t 训练系统
is we train the system at a specific time t as
我们要在特定时间 t 训练系统
well as take into account all that has happened before.
也要考虑之前发生的所有内容
For example, assume that we are at timestep, t equals 3.
例如假设我们位于时间步长 t 等于 3
Our square error remains as before the square of
我们的平方差仍然与之前相同
the difference between the desired output and the network output,
即理想输出和网络输出的方差
in this case at time t equals three.
在这个例子中时间 t 等于 3
This is the folded scheme at this particular time.
这是特定时间的折叠框架
To update each weight matrix,
为了更新每个权重矩阵
we need to find the derivatives of the loss function at time
我们要找出时间 t 等于 3 时损失函数的导数
t equals three as a function of all of the weight matrices.
作为整个权重矩阵的函数
In other words, we will modify each matrix using
换句话说我们要使用梯度下降修改每个矩阵
gradient descent just as we did before in feedforward neural networks.
就像我们之前在前馈神经网络中一样
But in addition, we also need to consider the previous timesteps.
不过另外我们还需要考虑之前的时间步长
To better understand how to continue with this process of back propagation through time,
为了更好理解如何继续使用基于时间的反向传播过程
we will unfold this model.
我们可以展开这个模型
All this, in the next video.
接下来视频中将介绍所有这些内容